So how was Joan?
조앤이랑 잘 돼가?
Broke up with her.
찢어졌어
왜?
Oh, why?
설마 그 큰 콧구멍 때문은
아니겠지?
Don't tell me.
Because of the big nostril thing?
They were huge!
말도 마! 재채기할 때마나
콧구멍이 주먹만해져
When she sneezed,
bats flew out of them.
They were not that huge.
그 정도는 아냐
I'm telling you, she leaned back,
I could see her brain.
나한테 기댔을 때 보니까
뇌가 보일 정도였다고
겉보습만 보고 여자를
갈아치운다는 거야?
How many women will you reject...
...over superficial,
insignificant things
잠깐, 잠깐만!
Hold it. I gotta side
with Chandler on this one.
난 이번 일에 대해선
챈들러 편이야
When I first moved here,
I went out with this girl.
처음 이 곳에 와서
여자를 사귀었을 때
Really hot. Great kisser...
엄청 화끈하고
키스 솜씨도 죽였는데
...but she had the biggest
Adam's apple.
목젖이 엄청 컸어
Drove me nuts.
도저히 못 봐주겠더라
-You or me?
-I got it.
- 누가 말할까?
- 내가 할게
Joey, women don't have Adam's apples.
조이, 여자에겐 목젖이 없어
지금 나 놀리는 거지?
You guys are messing with me, right?
맞아!
Yeah. We are!
That's a good one.
For a second there, I was like, whoa!
썰렁하진 않았어
깜빡 속을 뻔했거든
The One Where Heckles Dies
지금까지 정당한 이유로
헤어진 여자 있으면 대 봐
You name one woman that you broke up
with for an actual real reason.
Maureen Rasillo.
모린 로질로
Because she doesn't hate Yanni
is not a real reason.
야니를 좋아한다고 헤어진 건
정당하지 못하지
Hello, Mr. Heckles.
안녕하세요, 헤클스 씨
You're doing it again.
- 아무리 말해도 소용없군
- 저흰 안 그랬어요
We're not doing anything.
위에서 뛰어대니까
내 새가 경기 일으키잖아!
You're stomping.
It's disturbing my birds.
You don't have birds.
새 안 키우시잖아요
I could have birds.
키울 수도 있어
We'll try to keep it down.
조용히 할게요
고맙군, 가서 하던
디너 파티 마저 끝내야지
Thank you.
I'm going to rejoin my dinner party.
안녕히 가세요
All right, bye-bye.
Okay, Janice.
재니스!
이유 있어서 헤어졌잖아
Give me Janice.
That wasn't about being picky.
- 맞아
- 재니스는 인정!
We'll give you Janice.
I miss Janice, though.
재니스가 보고 싶어
Hello, Chandler Bing!
'안녕, 챈들러 빙'
Oh, my God!
'어머, 세상에나! '
Oh, Chandler!
'챈들러, 어서 해! '
Now! Now!
That's it.
'아이 좋아! 더 빨리! '
There! Faster!
Stop with the broom!
We're not making noise!
떠들지도 않았는데
왜 빗자루로 쳐대요!
We won.
- 우리가 이겼어
- 이겼다!
We did it!
Mr. Heckles!
헤클스 씨가...
- 어떻게 된 거죠?
- 청소하고 있었나 봐요
-How did this happen?
-He was sweeping.
They found a broom in his hand.
머리에 빗자루가 있었죠
세상에!
-That's terrible.
-I know.
- 정말 끔찍해요
- 누가 아니래요
I was sweeping yesterday.
나도 어제 청소했는데
내가 죽을 수도 있었죠
It could've been me.
그러게요!
Sweeping. You never know.
청소란 것이...
워낙 위험하잖아요
Never know.
그럼요
약하긴 하지만 아직도
그의 존재가 느껴져
It's very faint, but I can
still sense him in the building.
Go into the light, Mr. Heckles!
천당으로 올라가요, 헤클스 씨!
Okay, Phoebe.
그만 해, 피비
I'm sorry,
but sometimes they need help.
때론 귀신도 도움이 필요해
- 당근이지
- 누가 아니랬나...
Here we go.
좋아, 실컷 비웃어
That's fine, go ahead and scoff.
There are a lot of things
I don't believe in...
하지만 이 세상엔 믿을 수
없는 일들이 정말 많아
... but that doesn't mean
they're not true.
Such as?
예를 들면?
Like crop circles or
the Bermuda Triangle or evolution.
UFO, 버뮤다 삼각지
또는 진화라든지
잠깐
What, you don't believe in evolution?
진화론을 안 믿는다고 했어?
응, 난 못 믿겠어
Not really.
You don't believe in evolution?
진화론을 안 믿어?
I don't know.
It's just, you know....
글쎄, 뭐랄까...
다윈이고 원숭이고
Monkeys, Darwin, it's a nice story.
I just think it's a little too easy.
그럴 듯하지만
너무 간단하잖아
"Too easy"? Too
너무 간단해?
The process of every living thing
on this planet evolving...
단세포가 수백만 년의
진화를 거쳐서
...over millions of years from
single-celled organisms is "too easy"?
오늘날의 생물체가 된 게
너무 간단하다고?
Yeah, I just don't buy it.
응, 난 인정 안 해
Excuse me. Evolution is not
for you to buy, Phoebe.
미안하지만 진화론은
네 인정이 필요 없어
Evolution is scientific fact,
like the air we breathe...
진화는 과학적 사실이야
우리가 숨쉬는 공기나 중력처럼
...Iike gravity.
Don't get me started on gravity.
중력은 들먹이지도 마
중력도 안 믿어?
You don't believe in gravity?
Well, it's not so much that,
you know, I don't believe in it.
믿지 않는 게 아니라...
Lately I get the feeling that...
요샌 아무리 구부려도
당겨지지가 않더라고
...I'm not so much being pulled down
as I am being pushed.
Pushed.
It's lsaac Newton and he's pissed.
뉴튼이 화나서 쫓아왔어!
There she is. And over there,
that's the other one.
이 여자예요
저기도 한 명 있구요
This is Mr. Buddy Doyle,
Heckles' attorney.
헤클스 씨의 변호사인
버디 도일 씨인데
He'd like to talk to you.
할 얘기가 있으시대요
- 무슨 일이죠?
- 간단하게 말하죠
What can we do for you?
All right, kids, here's the deal.
According my client's will...
고인의 유언에 따라
그의 재산 상속자는...
... he wants to leave
all his earthly possessions...
...to "the noisy girls
in the apartment above mine."
'위층의 시끄러운 여자들'
What about his family?
- 가족은요?
- 가족은 없어요
He didn't have any.
Okay, so let's talk money.
그럼 돈 얘기나 하죠
돈은 없어요
일단 서명부터 해요
All right, there was none.
Now, let's talk signing.
You be noisy girl number one.
You be noisy girl number two.
시끄러운 여자 1번
시끄러운 여자 2번
I can't believe that this whole time
we thought he hated us.
우릴 싫어하는 줄 알았는데
Isn't it amazing how much
you can touch someone's life...
우리 자신도 모르게
남의 인생에 관여했다고
...without even knowing it?
이 꼴을 봐!
Would you look at this dump?
He hated us!
This was his final revenge!
우릴 너무나 싫어해서
마지막 복수를 한 거야!
I've never seen so much crap!
완전히 쓰레기장이야!
묘사가 좀 약하지 않아?
Actually, I think this apartment
sullies the good name of crap.
Check this out.
이것 좀 봐
Can I have this?
내가 가져도 돼?
How can you not believe in evolution?
어떻게 진화론을 안 믿어?
I don't know, just don't.
Look at this funky shirt!
그냥...
이 셔츠 끝내준다!
피비, 난 내 젊음을
진화론 연구에 다 바쳤어
Pheebs, I've studied evolution
my entire adult life.
전 세계를 돌아다니며
화석을 수집했는데
And we've collected fossils
from all over the world...
그건 다른 종의 진화를
뒷받침하는 증거라고!
...that actually show the evolution
of different species.
시간의 흐름과 더불어
I mean, you can literally see them...
...evolving through time.
진화하는 것을 눈으로
확인할 수 있다고
Really? You can actually see it?
정말?
눈으로 볼 수 있어?
You bet! In the U.S.,
China, Africa, all over!
그럼!
미국, 중국, 아프리카...
세계 어디서든지!
See, I didn't know that.
그건 미처 몰랐어
이제 알았으면 됐어
Well, there you go.
So now the real question is,
who put those fossils there and why?
그런데 문제는 그 화석들을
누가, 왜 거기 뒀냐는 거지
다들 이것 봐
'나의 불평 모음'
Look at this!
My Big Book of Grievances.
Hey, there's me!
내 얘기잖아!
"April 1 7th, excessive noise...
'4월 17일, 엄청 시끄러움'
... Italian guy comes home with a date."
'이탈리아 녀석이 애인과
집에 들어왔다'
You're in here too.
챈들러, 네 얘기도 있어!
"April 1 8th, excessive noise...
'4월 18일, 엄청 난리다'
... Italian guy's gay roommate
brings home dry cleaning."
'이탈리아 녀석 호모 애인이
빨래를 갖고 들어왔다'
Well, that's excellent.
정말 예리하군
Look at this lamp.
모니카, 이 램프 특이하지?
우리가 가져가자
Is this tacky or what?
We have to have this.
I think we have enough regular lamps.
지금도 우리에겐
평범한 램프가 많잖아
뭐 어때서?
What? Come on, it's not like...
이 누드 시계하고는
차원이 틀리잖아
... I'm asking for this
girlie clock or anything.
Which, by the way,
I also think is really cool.
이것도 괜찮아 보이네
Look, it doesn't go
with any of my stuff.
내 물건이랑 안 어울려
Well, what about my stuff?
그럼 내 물건은?
You don't have any stuff.
네 물건은 없잖아
You still think of it
as your apartment, don't you?
아직도 네 아파트라고
생각하는구나, 그렇지?
아냐
Yes, you do.
그렇잖아!
You think of it as your apartment
and I just rent a room.
날 네 아파트에 세든
세입자고 생각한다고
While you "mmm" on that,
I'll go find a place for my new lamp.
계속 버벅대고 있어
난 램프 갖다놓고 올게
Okay, Pheebs. See how I'm making
these little toys move?
피비, 장난감을 움직이는
내 손이 보이지?
마주보는 엄지!
Opposable thumbs!
진화론이 거짓이라면
이건 어떻게 된 거지?
Without evolution, how do you
explain opposable thumbs?
Maybe the Overlords needed them
to steer their spacecrafts.
하느님이 우주선 조정에
사용하려고 그랬나?
Tell me you're joking.
지금 농담하는 거지?
Look, can't we say that you believe
in something and I don't?
이렇게 생각하자고
이건 견해차일 뿐이야
-No, Pheebs, we can't.
-Why not?
- 그럴 순 없어
- 왜?
왜 모두를 네 생각에
동의하게 만들려고 하지?
What is this obsessive need
to make everybody agree with you?
No, what's that all about?
You know what I think?
대체 왜 그래?
아무래도 로스라는 세포를
현미경으로 관찰해 봐야겠다
I think maybe it's time
you put Ross under the microscope.
Is there blood coming out of my ears?
내 귀가 좀 이상한 거지?
헤클스 씨의 고등학교
졸업앨범이야
Check it out.
Heckles' high-school yearbook.
He looks so normal!
멀쩡하게 생겼었네
He's even kind of cute.
귀여울 정도야
"Heckles, you crack me up
in science class.
'헤클스, 과학 시간에
너무 웃겼어'
'넌 정말 웃긴 친구야'
You're the funniest kid in school."
-Funniest? Heckles?
-That's what it says.
- 헤클스가?
- 그렇게 써 있잖아
Heckles was voted class clown,
and so was l.
물건이었군
나도 그랬는데
헤클스 나무랄 것 없어
저 소릴 들어 보라고
He was right!
Would you listen to that?
엄청 시끄럽네
I'd call that excessive.
What?
왜?
Heckles played clarinet in band,
and I played clarinet.
헤클스 씨도 음악시간에
나처럼 클라리넷을 불었어
He was in the scale
modeler's club and I was
모형 제작반에서
특별활동을 했고, 난...
There was no club,
but I sure thought they were cool.
모임에 들진 않았지만
내가 동경하던 분야였어
So? You were both dorks.
그러고 보니 생긴 것도
닮은 것 같아
Big deal.
그게 뭘?
I just think it's weird, you know?
Heckles and me
이상하지 않아?
헤클스와 내가...
Heckles and me. Me
Me and Heckles.
나와 헤클스가...
Hey, would you knock it off!
그만 뛰어!
Have you been here all night?
밤새 여기 있었어?
Look at this.
이것 좀 봐
Pictures of all the women
Heckles went out with.
헤클스가 사귀었던
여자들 사진이야
Look what he wrote on them.
"Vivian, too tall."
밑에 적힌 걸 읽어 봐
'비비안은 너무 크고
매지는 잇몸이 다 보인다'
"Madge, big gums."
"Too loud."
'수다스럽고 너무 똑똑하고
밥 먹을 때 소리내고... '
"Too smart."
"Makes noise when she eats."
This is me.
나랑 똑같아!
나도 이렇다고
This is what I do.
I'm gonna end up alone,
just like he did.
이 사람처럼 나도 혼자
죽고 말 거야
헤클스는 미치광이였어
Heckles was a nut case.
Our trains are on the same track.
우린 같은 열차야
내가 30년 늦게 출발했지만
정거장은 다 똑같다고
I'm coming up 30 years behind him,
but the stops are all the same.
Bitter Town...
'매정한 마을'
...Alone-ville, Hermit Junction!
'쓸쓸한 마을'
'은둔자 마을'!
You know what we gotta do?
Get you out of here.
당장 여기서 나가자
내가 아침 살게
I'll buy you breakfast.
내 반쪽을 못 만나면?
아님 벌써 만났는데
What if I never find somebody?
Or worse, what if I found her...
... but I dumped her because
she pronounces it, "supposably"?
'아미도'라고 발음한다고
내가 벌써 차 버렸으면?
Chandler, come on,
you're gonna find somebody.
챈들러, 넌 좋은 여자를
만나게 될 거야
How do you know that? How?
그걸 어떻게 알지?
- 어떻게?
- 위로하려고 한 소리야
I don't know. I'm just
trying to help you out.
You guys will all get married...
너희는 모두 결혼하고
난 혼자 죽게 될 거야
...and I'll end up alone.
Will you promise me something?
약속해 줄래?
When you're married, will you
invite me over for holidays?
결혼하고 나서 연휴 때
나 집으로 초대해 줄래?
별 계획이 없으면
I don't know what we'll be doing.
I mean, what if we're over
at her folks' place?
아내가 친정에 가자면?
Yeah, I understand.
이해할게
You can come over
and watch the Super Bowl.
'슈퍼볼' 보러 놀러와
Every year, all right?
매년!
그럼 됐지?
You know what?
I'm not gonna end up like this.
분명히 말하지만
난 이렇게 안 될 거야
I'll see you, man.
참!
"Supposably."
'아미도'?
Supposably!
'아미도'라고?
Did they go to the zoo?
'동물원에 갔었대?'
Supposably.
'아미도'
Hi. It's me.
나야, 챈들러
어머 세상에나!
Oh, my God!
Janice? You called Janice?
재니스에게 전화를 했어?
Yes. Janice.
그래, 재니스
무슨 문제라도 있어?
Why is that difficult to comprehend?
You remember Janice, right?
재니스 기억하겠지?
Yes. She was smart, she was pretty
and she honestly cared about me.
그래, 예쁘고 똑똑하고
날 정말 좋아했어
Janice is my last chance
to have somebody.
재니스는 내 마지막 기회야
안녕?
어머 세상에나!
Oh, my God!
Jeez, look how fat she got.
엄청 뚱뚱해졌네
- 모두들 안녕?
- 어서 와
-Hey, it's everybody!
-Hi, Janice.
재니스, 배가...
Janice, you're....
그래, 맞아
Yes, I am.
혹시...
-ls it?
-ls it yours?
네 아기냐고?
꿈 깨, 챈들러 빙
You wish, Chandler Bing!
You are looking at a married lady now.
난 이제 유부녀라고
Congratulations.
축하해
자기야, 미안해
Sweetie, I'm sorry.
You couldn't tell me on the phone?
전화로 말하지 그랬어
And what? Miss the expression
on your face? Oh, no!
네 이 실망하는 표정을
놓치라고?
Janice likes to have her fun!
재니스는 좀 짓궂거든
You know what we haven't
played in a while?
레이첼, 오랜만에 게임 할까?
- 뭐?
-'램프 숨기기'
Hide the lamp.
Monica, let it go.
모니카, 이제 그만둬
Did you know
I'm allergic to shellfish?
난 조개 알레르기 있어
그럼 다른 램프를
잡아먹어
Then you'll just have
to eat the other lamps.
It's scary scientist man.
무서운 과학자 나리 듭시오!
Okay, Phoebe, this is it.
증거를 가져왔어
In this briefcase I carry
actual scientific facts.
이 가방엔 과학적 증거로
가득 차 있어
A briefcase of facts, if you will.
역사적 사실이 담긴 가방이야
Some of these fossils are
over 200 million years old.
몇몇 화석은 2억 년이
넘은 것들이지
다시 말해두지만
진화론을 부정하는 건 아냐
Before you even start,
I'm not denying evolution.
It's just one of the possibilities.
여러 가능성 중에서
하나란 말이지
유일한 가능성이야!
It's the only possibility.
마음을 요만큼만 열어 봐
Ross, could you just open
your mind, like, this much?
유명한 사상가들이 한때는
지구가 평평하다고 믿었지?
Didn't the brightest minds in
the world believe the Earth was flat?
And up till 50 years ago, you thought
the atom was the smallest thing...
50년 전까지만 해도
원자가 가장 작다고 했는데
...until you split it open
and this whole mess of crap came out.
까 보니까 별 잡동사니가
다 들어 있었잖아
그런데 이렇게 뻔뻔하게
Are you telling me that you are
so unbelievably arrogant...
...that you can't admit that
there's a teeny, tiny possibility...
네가 틀렸을 확률이
요만큼 존재한다는 것을
...that you could be wrong about this?
전혀 인정할 수 없다고?
There might be...
아마도
...a teeny...
아주 희박한...
가능성은 있겠지
...tiny...
... possibility.
I can't believe you caved.
이렇게 순순히 항복하다니
뭐?
You just abandoned
your whole belief system!
네 신념을 버렸잖아
네 이론에 동의는 안 해도
네 신념을 존경했었는데
Before, I didn't agree with you,
but at least I respected you.
But....
내일 어떻게 출근할래?
How are you gonna go
into work tomorrow?
How are you going to face
the other science guys?
다른 과학자들을
어떻게 쳐다볼 거야?
How are you going to face yourself?
네 자신은 어떻고?
That was fun.
So who's hungry?
너무 재밌다
밥 먹으러 갈래?
I am.
- 좋지
- 코트 입고 올게
Me too.
Let me just get my coat.
What happened?
맹세하지만 사고였어!
It was an accident, I swear.
재킷을 입는데
램프가 떨어졌어
I was putting on my jacket and
the thing and the lamp and it broke.
거짓말 마, 모니카
내 불쌍한 램프!
Oh, please, Monica!
You've always hated my lamp!
램프가 혼자 떨어져서
부서졌다고?
And now all of a sudden,
it's just magically, it's just broken?
Phoebe, tell her?
피비, 얘기 좀 해줘
I didn't see it, because
I was putting on my jacket.
난 옷 입느라 못 봤지만
네 말을 믿고 싶어
But I want to believe you.
Hey, Chandler. Monica just
broke my seashell lamp.
잘 왔어, 챈들러
모니카가 내 램프를 부셨어
Neat.
잘됐네!
난 혼자 죽을 거야!
I'm gonna die alone!
Okay, you win.
그래, 네가 이겼다
Chandler, you are not
gonna die alone.
챈들러, 넌 혼자 죽지 않아
Janice was my safety net, okay?
재니스는 내 안전망이었어
이제 뱀을 사야 한다고!
And now I have to get a snake.
그건 왜지?
Why is that?
If I'm gonna be an old, lonely man,
I'm gonna need a thing.
혼자 늙어가려면
무엇인가가 필요하잖아
You know, a hook.
그 갈고리!
자기 얼굴을 먹어치우는
지하철의 그 남자처럼
Like that guy on the subway
who eats his own face.
그래서 난 뱀을 가진
미치광이가 되기로 했어
So I figure I'll be
"Crazy Man With A Snake."
Crazy Snake Man.
Then I'll get more snakes,
call them my babies.
그리곤 뱀을 더 사서
자식새끼 삼으면
Kids will run past my place!
애들은 우리 집 앞을
뛰어 지나가겠지
"Run away from Crazy Snake Man,"
they'll shout!
'미친 땅꾼 영감이다! '
You've got to get over this.
이제 잊어버려
넌 혼자 되지 않을 거야
You won't end up alone.
혼자 될 거야
Of course I will.
I reject anyone who's crazy enough
to actually go out with me...
나랑 사귀겠다고 결심한
정신나간 여자들을
쓸모 없는 여자로 치부해
죄다 차 버렸잖아!
...and then I bitch that there
aren't any great women out there.
우리가 지금까지 사귄
남자들을 묘사해 줬어
You have just described...
...virtually every man
that we've ever gone out with.
넌 이상한 게 아냐
남자일 뿐이지
You are not a freak.
You're a guy.
She's right.
맞아, 딴 남자들하고
다를 게 없다고
You're no different than the rest.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Yes, he is.
잠깐만, 그렇지 않아
넌 완전히 달라
You are totally different.
In a bad way?
- 나쁜 쪽으로?
- 아니, 좋은 쪽으로
No, honey, in a wonderful way.
You know what you want now.
네가 원하는 게 뭔지 알잖아
Most guys don't even have a clue.
대부분의 남자들은
그것도 모른다고
You're ready to take risks, be
vulnerable and intimate with someone.
넌 누군가와 진지하게
사귈 준비가 됐어
You're not gonna end up alone.
넌 혼자 되지 않아
재니스에게 전화할 정도로
절박한 상황이잖아!
You called Janice. That's how much
you wanted to be with someone!
-You've made it!
-You're there!
- 네가 해냈어!
- 어른이 됐어!
You are ready to make a commitment!
결혼을 할 준비가 됐어!
Don't know about that!
그건 아직 몰라!
What you got there?
그건 뭐야?
Something else that's not yours
that you can break?
부셔도 괜찮은
또 다른 물건?
아니, 네가 좋아하니까
너 주려고
I know you like this
and I want you to have it.
우리 집에 잘 어울릴 거야
It'll look good in our apartment.
Thank you.
고마워
That's fine.
난 괜찮아
You'll all be pleased to know
that I have a date tomorrow night.
날 위해 기뻐해 주겠어?
내일 데이트하기로 했어
직장 동료 앨리슨이야
예쁘고 똑똑한데
This woman Allison from work.
She is great.
She's pretty, she's smart.
And I've been...
여태까지 내가 멀리했어
... holding off asking her out
in the past, because she has a...
... unusually large head.
머리가 좀 크거든
하지만 이제 그런 것에
신경 안 쓸 거야
But I'm not going to let
that stuff hang me up anymore.
좋았어!
Look at me. I'm growing.
난 철이 들었다고
졸업앨범도 재활용해?
You can't recycle yearbooks, can you?
I'll take that.
내가 가질게
You want his yearbook?
- 헤클스의 졸업앨범을?
- 그래
Some people said nice things about him.
Somebody should have it.
헤클스에 대해서 좋은
말이 많이 적혀 있거든
기분이 이상해
Gosh, this is so weird.
His whole life was in
this apartment and now it's gone.
그의 인생이 서린 곳이
텅 비어 버렸잖아
I think it would be nice if we just
took a few moments for Mr. Heckles.
헤클스 씨를 위해서
묵념의 시간을 갖자
He was kind of a pain.
He was, but he was a person.
좀 괴팍스럽기는 했지만
좋은 사람이었잖아
왜?
You're all going to hell.
모두 지옥에나 떨어져!
별로 커 보이지 않았어
It's really not that big!
- 네가 가지려고?
- 당근이지!
-Taking that with you, huh?
-Oh, yeah.
안 가?
You coming?
In a second.
조금만 있다 갈게
Goodbye, Mr. Heckles.
안녕, 헤클스 씨
We'll try to keep it down.
앞으로 조용히 할게요
My major was useless.
전공을 잘못 택했어요
How often do you look in the classifieds
and see "Philosopher Wanted"?
누가 철학전공자를
채용하려고 하겠어요?
Sure.
그래요
My God, that's a big head!
맙소사, 머리 엄청 크네
It didn't look this big in the office.
Maybe it's the lighting.
밖에서 보니 더 크잖아
조명 때문에 그런가?
My head must look
like a golf ball at work.
내 머리는 사무실에서
골프 공처럼 보일 거야
Don't get hung up on it. Quick!
List five things you like about her.
챈들러, 이럼 안 돼
좋은 점 다섯 가지 생각해
Nice smile, good dresser.
예쁜 미소, 옷 잘 입고...
가분수, 가분수, 가분수!
Big head, big head, big head!